Sai Rakesh Potnuru



rakeshpotnuru321@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/itsrakeshdotco



+917780231291



https://itsrakesh.co

Summary

I'm Rakesh Potnuru, a Full Stack Developer, Technical Writer, and a passionate learner. I am pursuing B.Tech in Computer Science and Engineering at Lovely Professional University, Punjab, India. I have worked on a wide range of technologies and have worked on projects ranging from small to large scale.

Experience



环 Team Member

Google Developer Student Club - LPU

Mar 2022 - Present (1 month +)

Peer-to-Peer learning and building solutions for local businesses and our community with Google technologies.

🕦 Hacker Noon Contributing Writer

HackerNoon

Dec 2021 - Present (4 months +)

Writing technical articles for the Hackernoon community.

Technical Writer

Aviyel

Mar 2022 - Present (1 month +)

Education



Lovely Professional University

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science 2020 - 2024

Skills

Web Development • React.js • Technical Writing • Research • JavaScript • Node.js • Python (Programming Language) • C++ • Leadership • English

Honors & Awards



Hackathon winner - Developer Days

Sep 2021

Won the developer days hackathon in the web development track.

Hackathon winner - Hack This Fall

Oct 2021

Won the Hack This Fall Hackathon for the "Best use of web monetization".

Hackathon runner up - Community Classroom

Dec 2021

Won 2nd prize for the "Best use of stream" at Cloud Native Hackathon organized by community classroom.